I have seen this pin on Agent J twice.
Once in Ngai Ka-yan's office.
Is it related to Ngai Ka-yan's death?
What does this logo stand for?
You have seen this logo before?
Three months ago, after Ngai Ka-yan died,
I arranged a program on TV.
(One week after the incident)
I put the online channel staff on the show
to see if we'll find any new leads.
Why do you have a script?
Netizens criticized Jarvis,
I must defend him.
Watch what you say, don't make things worse.
Welcome to Healthy Souls.
The recent talk of the town is definitely
the livestreaming of the murder
on J Weekly.
A lot of people claimed to be
emotionally distressed after watching
the livecast.
Today, we have with us Miss Wong,
a clinical psychologist,
Miss Ho, an educational psychologist,
Helen, the co-sponsor of the livecast
and Wendy and Paul from the online channel
to have a chat with us.
The image of Jarvis dropping to the floor
after he inhaled the oxygen
is still fresh on my mind.
Wendy's condition is very common.
With the advanced information technology,
people like to save videos and
send them out.
I'd like to appeal to everyone to stop it
and stop watching it again.
Repeated viewing will only increase
your emotional distress.
I want to say Jarvis was very talented.
He only wanted to bring people joy.
Unfortunately, he died in an accident.
Her reaction tells me she's a fan.
In recent years, it's common to make
videos of people playing tricks on others.
It's a hit among young people.
Miss Ho, what's your view on this trend?
Young people think pranks are harmless
and they trick each other.
Over time, they tend to make light
of the danger involved.
If we don't correct this mentality in time,
when they get older, it'll easily cause
serious consequences.
Hey, watch it!
Jarvis wanted us to deal with
the absurd with laughter.
His videos helped me get back on my feet.
She's a die-hard fan, not an ordinary fan.
Wendy was right.
Jarvis had good intentions.
But honestly, he often crossed the line.
That's why our channel will work with
the Rehab Club
to provide support to viewers
who were affected.
Paul is more sensible.
We'll set up an Emotional Support Group,
you're all welcome to join us.
Lok Hiu-sin never went to
the online channel.
We can rule her out.
When you make a video of a prank,
it's likely to cause physical harm or
even death,
to both the prankster and the victim.
It is also likely to traumatize those
who watched the video.
If anyone is emotionally distressed,
I suggest you consult a
clinical psychologist
It's this pattern again.
Why does she have a bracelet like that?
Gogo Sir, thanks for your suggestion,
or we wouldn't have consulted experts
to deal with the aftermath on TV.
Don't mention it.
Paul, will you continue to run the channel?
Miss Lok, can I ask you about this bracelet?
Helen! Didn't get a chance to talk earlier.
Are you busy? Let's have lunch.
Great!
You know each other?
Miss Ho was my counselor in high school.
She was a great help after my accident.
Sorry!
Let's go.
Hello, Ching Sir?
Gogo, I need you to check on something.
Come back to the Police station.
Yes, Sir!
It's been a while since I visited you
at school.
I didn't expect us to meet
under such circumstances.
I haven't seen Ngai Ka-yan for
so many years.
I can't believe when I hear about him again,
it was about his death.
Helen, when we were on air just now,
I noticed you were very nervous.
Are you upset?
No.
The livestreaming of the
Static Apnea Challenge
was a joint project by your Club
and the online channel.
Now that someone is dead,
you feel bad about it?
(Eight years ago)
Thanks.
Hey!
You're here. Good, practice with me.
Practice? Exams are coming up.
I'm not smart like you.
I need to study.
You spent too much time playing
video games.
Cramming in the last minute won't help.
I'm trying out for the Hong Kong Team
next week.
You'll be the goalie for me.
Again?
How about...I'll kiss you each time
you block the ball.
Right away!
Last one...if you fail, you'll get nothing.
Bring it on!
Even if I fail, you must kiss me.
Just once. I blocked many shots.
No!
Just once...
No, you didn't!
That's my bottle!
Your mouth touched my saliva,
that's an indirect kiss.
That's childish! You're not in grade school.
I wish we had met in grade school.
Then we could be childhood sweethearts.
Did you know ordinary water
has no electrolyte?
I'll get you something with electrolyte.
I'll go with you.
I also need to run to the toilet.
Are you OK?
Get up...
No...
Where are you hurt?
My back...
(0 Cycle Drain)
Ready for your housewarming present?
Aren't we moving together?
Is the present for me or for yourself?
Just take a look.
I'm unveiling it...
Most people put up a starry sky,
why do we have the Hong Kong map?
Remember this place?
It's where we went on our first date.
Of course I remember.
Others go shopping, see a movie
or eat out on a date.
We're out in the boonies.
If I ask other people to go to
the Geopark with me,
they'll say I'm a bore.
Only you would go anywhere with me,
no matter how far away it is.
You know it's boring too?
Your dream is to become a geologist.
Of course I'd help you realize your dream.
Too bad I can't walk
and I can't go to Yellowstone Park with you.
Silly.
I'm just happy enjoying the breeze
at Wong Shek Pier.
Though I can't walk,
I can still go places with you.
Then I'm giving you this Hong Kong map.
(Eight years later)
When you're bored during your dialysis
at night,
you can look at it to kill time.
Let me help you.
No, I can manage.
Your clothes are here...
I'm going to the US next week.
I probably won't be back anytime soon.
Send me loads of pictures.
You plan to stay here?
You're not moving back in with Auntie?
No. I should learn to be more independent.
I don't want to be anyone's burden.
Thanks for looking after me
these past eight years.
You're not a burden to anyone.
You're the most important person in my life.
Don't worry about me. Go pursue your dream.
It's time for my appointment.
Take care.
Hi, Auntie Ching! Long time no see.
Well? Same as usual?
Oh...right!
I think you're amazing.
You have been buying pork from me
for so long
and you haven't gained an inch.
What? Oh, thanks...
Auntie Ching, what's wrong?
You forgot your change!
Where's the boyfriend?
He didn't come with you?
There's no need to bother him every time.
That's true.
The report shows your renal failure
is getting worse.
I also noticed your ostomy is
slightly infected.
I fell down a while ago.
Your crushing injury eight years ago,
caused muscle fibers to break down
and resulted in rhabdomyolysis and
you require dialysis.
You must be careful with the ostomy.
Persistent inflammation may
lead to complications.
Dr. Yuen, there's no other treatment?
Honestly, medication and dialysis
can only cure the symptoms, not the cause.
I suggest you register for
a kidney transplant.
You've been so helpful...here, my treat.
Thanks, Miss Ho.
I'm truly grateful to you
for taking time from your busy schedule
to play with SEN kids.
Working at the Rehab Club,
I often come across students with
Special Educational Needs.
They need a lot of tender loving care.
Yes, that's why you must play with them
more often.
They adore a big sister like you.
I will when I have time.
Helen, you still have such a
sunny personality.
Even when you have problems of your own,
I saw you had fun with the kids just now.
I counselled you for six years
I watched you injured yourself
when you were in Form 6,
came back to school and went on to college.
I know exactly what you're thinking.
The brighter the sun, the bigger the shadow.
I broke up with Ching.
I moved in with my boyfriend a year ago.
We were quite happy.
Sorry, I was late getting off work.
Let me help you.
No, I can manage. Your work is important.
I know you want to be independent.
But this concerns your health.
Let me help you.
(Please wait)
(0 Cycle Drain)
Wait while I prepare dinner.
But as I watched this First Honor
Geology major,
who doesn't spend his time doing research,
but takes care of me and my dialysis,
it breaks my heart.
Hello? I know the results came out.
Yes...I didn't have time to go back
to the office.
OK, I'll follow up tomorrow.
OK...thank you...bye!
You really must try this egg.
I seldom make it so perfect. Try it.
Remember what day is next week?
Our 8th anniversary.
Yes. I have everything planned out.
We're not going to Wong Shek Pier.
Then let's go to Yellowstone Park.
You want to go away? OK.
But you must wait till
I'm not so busy at work.
No, I'm not waiting for you.
And you should stop waiting for me.
What's wrong? You're not feeling well?
I don't want you to waste your life away
because of me.
Don't be silly...you are my life.
I saw the letter from Professor Chan.
He pulled some strings for you
so you can do research work in the US
for a professor you admire.
Yes, I got a letter from him,
but I haven't said yes.
Professor Chan thought I have the
right qualifications,
and sent out my CV without asking me.
Do you want to go?
Ching, your world should be Yellowstone Park
not Wong Shek Pier.
But I don't want to leave you.
Go pursue your dream.
So you brought it up?
I thought it was just puppy love between you
I never expected it to last this long.
If we hadn't been through
thick and thin together,
ours should have been puppy love
and we would have broken up.
Your accident was such a major blow to you.
I thought it was an accident too,
until recently...
On behalf of the Rehab Club,
I had a meeting with people from J Weekly.
And I saw him again.
Because the livestreaming was a fundraiser,
I had to do my homework
and know more about the background
and characteristics of J Weekly.
I found one of the older videos
Jarvis made for his channel.
I watched it carefully...
Watch it, don't kill yourself!
It was identical to what happened to me.
At first, I thought I missed a step
and I landed on the ground.
But watching the video of that
fishing line football,
it reminded me when I fell,
the football moved away.
It was likely someone pulled it away.
But I was in so much pain I didn't notice.
Are you OK?
Get up...
No...
Where are you hurt?
My back...
Before the accident, I saw him
in the playground.
It's very likely he was the prankster
who paralyzed me.
He acted on a whim to pull a prank,
you ended up in a wheelchair
and needed dialysis.
He used to trick people for fun.
Then evolved into fishing for likes and
online traffic
and he continued to hurt people.
For a bunch of numbers,
he got himself killed in the end.
Is it worth it?
We zeroed in on Tsang Chun-kit and
Hung Tzi-long,
now this Director Tsui came from nowhere.
But we have no evidence to link him
to Ngai Ka-yan's death.
On the set of Healthy Souls,
I noticed the logo on Lok Hiu-sin's bracelet
is identical to the pin found in
Ngai Ka-yan's office.
I also noticed Lok Hiu-sin seemed
very uptight during the shoot.
Lok Hiu-sin and Ngai Ka-yan
only worked on this fundraiser,
why did she kill him?
Wow, this woman is vicious.
Her ex-boyfriend betrayed her ten years ago.
She held a grudge,
spent ten years to plan her revenge
and killed the ex.
Find out how Lok Hiu-sin became paralyzed.
Officers, this is Miss Ho.
Take your time.
Thank you.
Right!
Can I help you, Officers?
I remember you said on TV,
young people are immature
and often overlook the danger of a prank.
When they grow up, the consequence
could be unthinkable.
Ngai Ka-yan was one of your students,
can you tell us what he was like back then?
Ngai Ka-yan was very naughty
and often pulled pranks on his classmates.
We had a lot of complaints about him.
When Ngai Ka-yan was in high school,
he wasn't too popular among
his classmates, right?
No, he wasn't.
He wasn't mean or anything.
His pranks were quite harmless.
Did his harmless pranks
ever lead to anything disastrous?
Yes, someone got hurt.
Was it Lok Hiu-sin?
Are you suggesting Helen is involved
in Ngai Ka-yan's case?
Just answer my question.
All I can say is that,
Helen has a kind heart.
She would never intentionally hurt anyone.
Regarding your questions,
because they involve my students' privacy,
I'm sorry I can't disclose anything.
Miss Ho has such a tight trap.
That's not what I think.
Miss Ho's reaction already told me
we're on the right track.
Lok Hiu-sin is paralyzed because
of Ngai Ka-yan.
I can't believe they went to
the same high school,
just different grades.
Lok Hiu-sin was an outstanding athlete
with good prospects.
She's now paralyzed because of
Ngai Ka-yan's prank.
Revenge was her motive to kill him.
But she never went to the channel
and she wasn't at the scene
during the livestreaming.
Maybe someone at the channel
is her accomplice.
Gogo Sir, let's bring her in
for questioning.
Not yet. If she had an accomplice,
this person must have a close
relationship with her.
Shopping?
Hi, how are you?
Boss!
Hi! Lean pork and pig knuckles for you.
Thank you.
Well? How are you going to cook
your pork knuckles?
I'm just getting them for a friend
from the Rehab Club.
I see.
Sin!
Mom!
Auntie Ching?
I bought a chicken.
Pork and chicken are both high in protein.
Your skin will be silky soft.
You're such a sweet talker.
I don't know why either,
I'm always happy to see her.
My daughter takes after me.
Way back when, I was Ms. Sunshine in
Tai Hom Village and San Po Kong.
They appear to be mother and daughter.
If they're mother and daughter
then Lok Hiu-sin has a motive for murder.
Maybe they plotted Ngai Kan-yan's murder.
What's the occasion? Why the extra dishes?
Today is my last day.
Since I can finally take a break
after working for so long,
I thought we should celebrate.
But you sound so sad.
Still thinking about Jarvis?
No, I stopped thinking about it. It's over.
You should too.
The key is to get well.
I know.
We assumed Auntie Ching had no motive.
But now we know she's Lok Hiu-sin's mother
and there's such a grudge between
Lok Hiu-sin and Ngai Ka-yan.
But Auntie Ching worked for the
online channel for so many years,
she wouldn't need to wait this long
to make a move.
Maybe Lok Hiu-sin ran into Ngai Ka-yan
only because of the recent fundraiser,
and just found out he paralyzed her.
If Auntie Ching knew
she worked for the enemy for so long,
she's likely to fall apart.
A grassroot working mom with a pretty
and capable daughter
who found out someone paralyzed
her daughter,
can't possibly pretend nothing happened.
How did Auntie Ching do it?
She was at the office of the channel
at lunch time.
She claimed she was in the pantry
with her headphone on
and didn't know when the vase was broken.
During that time frame,
no one really knew her exact location.
She could have gone into Ngai Ka-yan's
office to swap the cylinder
and accidentally knocked over the vase.
During the livestreaming,
Auntie Ching was not at the pool,
she had the perfect alibi
and can frame Tom and Paul.
Ko Sir, what does a cleaning lady
know about H2S, hydrogen sulfide?
We're talking about making poisonous gas.
Brother Cheong, don't forget,
her daughter is an A student in science.
Anyone who knows about the danger
of swamp gas
would know what hydrogen sulfide is.
You're saying Auntie Ching acted alone
and Helen is her accomplice?
Right now, the key is to find out
how they got their hands on the H2S,
then we can prove they're the killers.
Maybe like Tom and Paul,
DIY in a factory building?
(Government Laboratory)
Please come this way.
These are stink bombs.
And this is the one you want to see most,
a high concentration of H2S.
Thanks.
Check the manufacturer of
the gas cylinder.
Find out where they sold this lot.
(University Lab)
Ko Sir, Lee Sir, when we got your inquiry,
we started checking
and found out your gas cylinder
came from our lab.
Why so many?
From different manufacturers.
These are all highly concentrated H2S.
This is the one in the picture you sent us.
I guess your tight security
can prevent people from wandering around?
You're quite right.
That's why we don't usually count
our gas cylinders.
Has anything been missing lately?
We took stock after we got your call,
five cylinders of H2S are missing.
Can you show my colleague your CCTV?
I want to know if anyone suspicious
was lurking around the lab.
I also need a roster of your lab staff.
Gogo Sir, CCTV showed no forced entry.
Security also double checked,
there was no sign of burglary.
It's probably an inside job.
Well? You found anything on the roster?
Auntie Ching is not on the cleaning staff.
Lok Hiu-sin is also not on the list.
What about staff from the online channel?
Nope.
Another dead end. I thought we'd find
new leads.
Ginseng chicken smells great.
I'm so blessed.
I haven't seen this look in a long time.
I just had dinner with you two weeks ago.
But it wasn't just us.
He was here the whole time...
I'll be home for dinner more often.
I better stock up on meal replacements.
The way you feed me, I'll gain weight.
I'll think about what to cook for you.
None of this would be a burden
to your kidneys.
This is great.
You just went to your follow-up appointment,
what did the doctor say?
What's wrong? You seem preoccupied.
Nothing.
What are you not telling me? Say it.
Because of Ching?
Why didn't you tell me
you broke up with him?
That creep, he's worried you can't
manage on your own,
he already gave me the heads up.
He said he's working for a professor abroad.
Mom, that's his dream.
He already put it off long enough for me.
I brought it up. Don't blame him.
He promised to take care of you
for the rest of his life.
That's why I let you move in with him.
If I knew he was just like your loser father
I would never have agreed to it.
I was happy these past eight years.
From the day of my injury,
I knew Ching would leave me eventually.
I already gained eight years. I'm content.
Only you would still defend him.
It's entirely that creep's fault
for doing this to you.
(One week before the incident)
I don't want any more treatments.
The world is so unfair.
Mom, we work so hard.
What about Ngai Ka-yan?
For what he did to hurt other people,
he's doing better and better.
Ngai Ka-yan? My boss Jarvis?
I just found out my injury
was not an accident.
It was one of Ngai Ka-yan's pranks
that paralyzed me.
Ngai Ka-yan, you scumbag...
Forget it, Mom! He's dead.
He got his retribution.
You and I will always have each other.
It's good that your Dad and Ching are gone.
Let's live our lives well, OK?
What a silly girl!
I'm glad I still have you.
Why don't you move back home with me?
Your legs have inflammation.
They just got better this past year
after I moved out.
You want a relapse and make me worry?
I'm worried about you living
out there alone.
You're not worried I'll have a heart attack?
OK...I made up my mind.
You're sleeping over tonight.
Why are you irritable? That's so unlike you.
Because you won't listen to me.
You think I'm still young?
How much longer can I work?
If only I could still cook for you
and take care of my precious daughter
one day at a time,
I'll be perfectly content.
But the dialysis machine is at home.
We'll go get it right after dinner.
Call the landlord tomorrow
and terminate your lease.
OK...whatever you say.
What's wrong? Not used to sleeping here
after so long?
No, I keep having nightmares.
What did you dream of?
I was back in the playground in high school.
I could still walk and run
and I was running around with my classmates.
Suddenly, a pair of hands reached out
from underground and grabbed my legs
and won't let me go.
I screamed for help and people ignored me.
Were those Jarvis' hands?
I thought so. But I couldn't see.
I hope he's not giving me nightmares
now that he's dead.
Think nothing of it.
A creep like him shooting videos of
pranks he pulled on people,
will get himself killed eventually
even if it didn't happen this time.
What are you looking at? It's late.
Each time I can't sleep,
I'd bring out the photo album
and look at old photos
to see how hard I worked
to raise my precious daughter.
If I survived then,
all the unhappy things seem trivial.
Thanks, Mom!
I'm sorry, if I didn't end up like this,
your life could have been wonderful.
It's wonderful enough.
See?
Oops...I guess it's not as
wonderful as I have imagined.
It's OK, let you and your future husband
fill in the rest.
Let's not wait. Let's fill it up now.
If Director Tsui doesn't want to run it,
let's clear out Jarvis' office...
No! Nobody touches Jarvis' things.
Wendy, he's gone.
Even if he was your idol...
He's not my idol, he's the hero
who saved my life.
When I was in high school,
I was bullied every day.
Are you OK? Did we hit you?
You have such a good figure,
why didn't you dodge?
She meant to but couldn't do it in time.
All the nutrients went over there,
making them so heavy, it'll take longer.
Oh dear, she'll become a moron.
She may have a lot of shortcomings,
but she has one virtue.
She can send out sexual vibes
so the boys will block the ball for her.
That's beyond your comprehension.
Let's play ball.
Sorry to interrupt.
All I could do back then was cry.
The only thing that cheered me up
was when Jarvis posted new videos.
Then one time, in one of the videos
I saw the boy whom I hated most.
1...2...3... pull!
I was beaming when classmates
laughed at him.
Since that day, Jarvis became my hero.
I joined the online channel
so I can become Robin to Jarvis' Batman.
But Batman wouldn't want Robin
to go on like this.
What would he want Robin to do?
Pull yourself together
and do something meaningful.
For example, finish what he started...
Can I?
Wendy! Are you Wendy?
I've been following you. Can we have a word?
I don't know you.
I have nothing to say to you.
I have something that
you'll be very interested in.
Hey...
Wendy...
Stop it! She said she doesn't know you.
No, Wendy! You'll want to see this.
Wendy...what are you doing? Wendy!
(One week later)
Honey, there's no point filling up
the photo album on purpose.
Everything is paid for. You must show up.
Still. We didn't have to dress up like this.
You said you wanted more memories.
OK, let me choose the last outfit.
Mom, this is an extreme challenge.
A qipao is impossible to carry.
Your grandma and I once went to a studio
and took pictures in a qipao.
Now that we have this chance,
I'd like to do the same.
When you have a daughter,
you must bring her to a studio
and take pictures in a qipao.
Even if I had son, I'd force him to come
and the three of us can take pictures.
I can't wait for that day.
Sin? Sin!
What's wrong?
Get us an ambulance! Please...
Sin...
Call for an ambulance...
Doctor, why did my daughter pass out?
The ostomy of Miss Lok's tube for dialysis
has been infected.
The inflammation gave her a fever,
she passed out because
she didn't have enough rest.
I'll prescribe antibiotics and antipyretics
for her and she'll be fine.
Thank you, Doctor.
She's in the queue for a kidney transplant,
be careful and make sure her condition
doesn't deteriorate.
Thank you.
Why didn't you tell me you need
a kidney transplant?
You didn't want to become a burden to me?
That's why you insisted on getting
the photo shoot.
Hiu-sin! Auntie Ching!
Dr. Yuen!
Dr. Yuen, I'm glad to see you.
From now on, please keep me posted
of my daughter's condition.
She's so willful, not until she passed out,
she didn't tell me she needed
a kidney transplant.
Mom!
Dr. Yuen, why are you here?
I have news for you.
What is it?
It's good news.
I told Hiu-sin about a new technology
in Switzerland.
I just heard back from them,
they accepted Hiu-sin for their
clinical trial.
What new technology?
Implanting electrodes that contain
spinal fluid into the brain
to reconnect the paralyzed patient's
brain and lower body.
In short, if it's successful,
Hiu-sin can walk again.
Oh dear, if you won't tell me the bad news,
at least tell me the good news.
Since I don't know if they'll accept
my application,
I didn't want to get excited over nothing.
This piece of news is making my adrenaline
or something...
I don't know...I can't describe
my excitement.
Mom!
Will you go with me?
You told me before not to think too much.
You may not get used to living in Europe,
but if we don't go now,
there might not be another chance.
I will.
I'll definitely go with you.
I don't have time for crazy fans.
Don't make me block...
Don't you want to know who held
a grudge against Jarvis?
Who are you?
I'm Jason, a diehard fan of yours
and Jarvis'.
Why should I believe you?
I'm a student at Jarvis' alma mater.
The day before he died,
I recorded his argument with someone
at the school.
Enjoy.
I thought you wanted to discuss
the fundraiser.
I didn't know you were a fellow alumnus.
Did you say the Alumni Association is here?
I attended all the functions.
How come I never saw you?
You haven't been back in a long time?
I don't remember.
This place hasn't changed much.
The teachers who taught us are gone.
Only Miss Ho is left.
When I had the accident at school,
Miss Ho has been a great help.
How sad! You have been paralyzed since
high school?
Before the accident, I was on the
school football team.
One day, I was practicing by myself.
I kicked a football tied to a fishing line,
I landed on my back and became like this.
You hooked the football to a fishing line.
That was you?
You knew all along?
I found out after I met you.
To me, I'm not seeking any justice.
I don't know what you intend to do
with the Static Apnea Challenge,
I only want you to cancel the prank.
I don't want anyone else to get hurt.
Stick to your original intention...
fundraising.
Look Lady, your organization put in
a lot of money for this show.
Surely you want it to be effective.
With good effects, you have viewership,
and you'll be able to raise more money.
I'd rather raise less money
than advocate this trend.
If you feel a shred of guilt
for paralyzing me...
I think you're quite mistaken.
I don't feel guilty at all.
I have done the fishing line football
at least a dozen times,
no one else was paralyzed like you.
Rather than blame me for
having gone too far,
blame your own rotten luck.
You don't think you're accountable at all?
Even if you survived that fall,
if you were destined to be paralyzed,
you still couldn't have dodged it.
How could you argue in all righteousness?
Because I'm the victim here.
Why can't you look at this from
my perspective?
I came up with these pranks
because I want recognition.
But everyone thought you had an accident.
It took you years to find out
I pulled a prank on you.
Did you realize that was the biggest insult
to an artist?
You're out of your mind.
I'm not talking to a lunatic
Yes!
You're crazy!
You simply don't understand the meaning
of these pranks to me.
You're only fixated on how I hurt people.
Wake up!
People get hurt in accidents every day.
Should we just stay home and do nothing?
That would be no different from
being paralyzed.
The essence of pulling pranks on others
is to make use of someone's misfortune
in exchange for laughter.
That's why only if I keep
pulling pranks on people without end,
will I be able to live up to the past
eight years you have been paralyzed.
Mom, how nice of you to pick me up
from work.
We're getting on the plane tomorrow night.
I don't know if the food overseas
is any good.
That's why we should have a feast tonight.
I was wondering about your relationship
with Jarvis.
Turns out you're Auntie Ching's daughter.
Helen, there are still transition documents
you haven't signed.
Go get your work done.
Since I forgot to buy a neck pillow,
I'll go get it now.
When you're done, we'll meet back home, OK?
Yes!
You're crazy!
You simply don't understand the meaning
of these pranks to me.
You must have killed Jarvis!